4K资源来源:Hao4k影音
-专注4K家庭影音, 服务千万发烧友-
更多4K蓝光原盘:www.Hao4k.vip
有一群人称自己为“公司”
There's a group of men called The Firm.
他们已经运作很长很长时间了
They've been running things for a long, long time.
当他们需要有人去清理麻烦时...
And when they need someone to clean up their mess...
...他们就派我去
...they send me.
火   药   奶   昔
去拿你的头盔 我们去商店
Go get your helmet. Let's go to the store.
你真可爱 小傻瓜
You look so cute, Nit.
- 山姆  - 内森
- Sam.  - Nathan.
- 你在哪里?  - 在家里 做缝纫
- Where are you?  - At home. Sewing.
在餐厅等我
Meet me at the diner.
为啥?
Why?
我有多少麻烦事?
How much trouble am I in?
给我最喜欢的客人多加了一勺
An extra scoop for my favorite client.
谢谢 萝丝
Thanks, Rose.
15         年         前
给我最喜欢的客人多加了一勺
I put in an extra scoop for my favorite client.
- 谢谢 萝丝  - 她很快就会来的
- Thanks, Rose,  - I'm sure she won't be long.
你显然不太了解我妈妈
You clearly don't know my mother very well.
嘿 陌生人
Hey, stranger.
- 要我帮你减负吗?  - 今天没带 萝丝
- Can I lighten your load?  - Not carrying today, Rose.
凡事都有第一次 她在那边
There's a first time for everything. She's over there.
谢谢你一直照看她
Thanks for keeping an eye on her.
你说你30分钟后到
You said you'd be here in 30 minutes.
我迟了几分钟
I'm a few minutes late.
迟到三个小时
Three hours.
你流血了
You're bleeding.
不过是工作日常 你带来了吗?
Just another day at the office. Did you bring it?
安娜·梅当然会选它们
Anna May sure can pick them.
- 已上膛  - 好姑娘
- It's loaded.  - Good girl.
听着 我必须离开一段时间
Listen, I, um... have to disappear for a while.
- 我和你一起去  - 不 这次不行
- Then I'm coming with you.  - You can't. Not this time.
内森马上就到 我走后他来照顾你
Nathan will be here soon. He'll take care of you when I'm gone.
- 我不想跟内森走  - 我这么做是为你好
- I don't want to go with Nathan.  - I'm doing this for your own good.
我会和安娜·梅还有其他人呆在图书馆里
I'll stay in the library with Anna May and the others.
那样太危险
It's too dangerous.
怎么了?
What's going on?
原因很复杂
It's... it's complicated.
告诉我
Tell me.
我不是小孩子了
I'm not a kid any more.
不 你是
No, you're not.
你没动你的奶昔
You haven't touched your milkshake.
我不想你不在就喝
Didn't want to drink it without you.
你要走多久?
How long will you be gone?
我得去打个电话
I have to make a quick phone call.
待在这儿
Stay here.
晚上好 先生们 能帮你们减负吗?
Evening, gentlemen. Can I lighten your load?
- 滚开  - 嘿
- Get lost.  - Hey.
你好 小女孩
Hello, little girl.
妈妈说不能和陌生人说话
Mommy says I'm not allowed to talk to strangers.
这个“妈妈”很像你
This "Mommy" looks a lot like you.
只是更大只更厉害
Only bigger and more stabby.
她身上全是我父亲的血
Got my father's blood all over her.
我不喜欢你
I don't like you.
玩够了
Enough games.
她在哪?
Where is she?
你真讨厌
Go kiss a pig.
告诉我她在哪里
Tell me where she is.
闭上眼睛 小宝贝
Close your eyes, baby girl.
妈妈
Mom!
♪ 昨日 ♪
♪ Yesterday ♪
♪ 你得过且过 ♪
♪ Any way you made it was just fine ♪
♪ 把你的日子耗费在夜晚 ♪
♪ So you turn your days into nighttime ♪
♪ 难道你不知道 ♪
♪ Didn't you know ♪
♪ 不去尝试何来的成功 ♪
♪ You can't make it Without ever even trying ♪
♪ 但你是有其他想法的 不是吗?  ♪
♪ And something's on your mind Isn't it? ♪
♪ 让这些时间...  ♪
♪ Let these times... ♪
晚上好 亲爱的
Evening, darling.
- 能帮你减负吗?  - 我没带
- Can I lighten your load?  - I'm clean.
是一直没带还是来餐厅没带?
Regular clean or diner clean?
- 把这个忘了  - 当然 甜心
- Forgot about this one.  - Of course, sugar.
- 是的  - 是啊
- Yeah.  - Yeah.
孩子
Boy.
史塔西：前东德秘密警察机构
噢 这些女孩比史塔西还狠
Oh, these girls are worse than the Stasi.
你受伤了吗?
You hurt?
只是工作日常
Just another day at the office.
哇 你说话就像你妈妈
Wow, you sound just like your mother.
我没有妈妈
I don't have a mother.
哦 但你肯定有她的脾气
Well, you sure have her temper.
今晚到底怎么回事?
What the hell happened tonight?
情报有误
Bad intel.
你说有四五个带枪的傻瓜
You said four or five idiots with peashooters.
对 然后呢?
Yes. And?
噢 上帝啊 孩子
Oh, for Christ's sake, child.
做这个应该低调行事 不要搞得腥风血雨
This was supposed to be low-profile, not a bloody massacre.
下次 我就让他们朝我开枪
Next time, I'll just let them shoot me.
下次 照我说的做
Next time, just do what you're told.
记住你为谁工作 只要他们开心就好...
Remember who you're working for. As long as they're happy...
你这么急打电话给我就为说这个?
You called me here oh-so-urgently just to remind me of that?
不是
No.
你的本事马上就会派上用场
Your talents are needed, pronto.
有人偷了我们的东西
Somebody stole from us.
谁疯到竟然偷公司的东西?
Who's crazy enough to steal from The Firm?
一个不知道我们是谁的人
Somebody who doesn't know who we really are.
是负责做假账的会计
An accountant. From the clean side of the business.
他偷了多少钱?
How much did he take?
足够让你去拜访他
Enough to earn a visit from you.
我们要拿回那些钱
We need that money back.
好姑娘
Good girl.
我稍后把地址发给你
I'll text you the address later.
噢 把你老掉牙的武器扔掉
Oh, and get rid of those stone-age firearms you carry.
- 我已经用好些年了  - 去找个开放供应商
- I've had them for years.  - Find an open vendor.
弄些干净的装备
And get yourself some clean boomsticks.
别让你和你留在现场的东西有关联 好吗?
We can't have you linked to that war zone you left behind, can we?
你知道我儿子背地里都在做什么吗?
Did you know about this little endeavor my son had on the side?
抱歉 叔叔 我不知道
Sorry, Uncle. I had no idea.
鞋子呢?
Where's the shoe?
什么鞋?
What shoe?
我儿子左脚现在没穿鞋
The shoe that is not currently covering my son's left foot.
看起来像右脚那只
The one that looks like the right one.
那只该死的鞋
That fucking shoe.
- 我不知道  - 那么 找到它
- I don't know.  - Well, find it.
找到了 麦克莱斯特先生
Found it, Mr. McAlester.
别跟他妈妈说这件事
Nobody tells his mother about this.
我会告诉她 他和某个女孩私奔了
We'll tell her he ran off with some girl.
知道了
I get it.
现在 去把杀我儿子的人的头拿来
Now, bring me the heads of the men that killed my boy.
嗯
Hmm.
你好 亲爱的
Hello, dear.
有什么事吗?
What can I do for you?
我想换一些... 书
I need to exchange some... books.
嗯 很好
Well, that's nice.
如今你这年纪的人很少看书了
Not a lot of people your age read nowadays.
- 你有我们的书卡吗?  - 没有
- Do you have a card with us?  - No.
我想办一张
I'd like to open one.
好极了
Wonderful.
你对哪类... 书感兴趣?
What kind of... books are you interested in?
这些书都太薄
Mostly smaller ones.
我要些大部头书
A few heavies.
哦 你在这里找不到那种
Well, you won't find them there.
这些是儿童读物
Those are our children's sections.
魔法森林...
The Enchanted Forest...
和无尽的海洋
and The Never-Ending Ocean.
听起来很有趣
They sound like fun.
我们以前见过吗?
Have we met before?
你看起来很... 面熟
You seem so... familiar.
不好意思 我有段时间没来图书馆了
I'm embarrassed to say it's been a while since I visited a library.
哦 亲爱的 那不是生活方式
Well, that's no way to live, dear.
让我给你找一本好书
Let's get you into a good book.
来吧
Come.
安娜·梅 这位可爱的小姐想在我们这儿开个帐户
Anna May, this lovely young lady wants to open an account with us.
哦
Well,
玛德琳应该告诉你
Madeleine should have told you
没有推荐人 我们不接纳新读者
that we don't accept new readerswithout a reference.
玛德琳有预感
Madeleine had a hunch.
如果你不介意我的法语 就忽悠你的预感吧
Fudge your hunches, if you pardon my French.
- 严格来说不是法语  - 总是字面意思
- Technically not French.  - Always literal.
- 对 我爱好文学 是图书管理员  - 也许是吧
- Yes, I'm literary. I'm a librarian.  - Be that as it may.
弗洛伦丝 亲爱的
Florence, dear.
你愿意加入我们吗?
Would you join us?
恐怕我们需要一个破局者
I'm afraid we need a tie-breaker.
玛德琳认为这个女孩需要读点书
Madeleine thinks this girl needs to do some reading.
我告诉过你我有预感
I told you I had a hunch.
她有些地方很眼熟
There's something very familiar about her.
又是预感 废话
Hunch, smunch.
另一方面 我认为我们该先厘清组织
I, on the other hand, think we should dispose of the body
再仔细讨论我们的加入协议
and then have a long talk about our onboarding protocols.
你知道我能听懂你们说的 对吧?
You know I can hear you, right?
安静 姑娘
Hush, girl.
别这么没礼貌
Don't be rude.
转过身来 亲爱的
Turn around, hon.
把帽子摘下来
And take off your hat.
你说你叫什么名字?
What did you say your name was?
她没说
She didn't.
嗯 真奇怪
Hmm. That's odd.
哦 姑娘?
Well, girl?
无言以对了吗? 说吧
Cat got your tongue? Speak up.
我是山姆
It's Sam.
斯佳丽的孩子
Scarlet's kid.
对
Yeah.
我就知道 忘不了那双眼睛
I knew it. Never forget those eyes.
自从你长大后 我们就没见过你了
We haven't seen you since you were yea high.
你妈妈好吗?
How is your mother?
15年没见过她了
Haven't seen her in 15 years.
哦 这是我们的共同点
Well, that's something we both have in common.
天哪 天哪 小山姆
My, my, my. Little Sam.
我们经常听说你
We hear about you all the time.
你已经名声大噪了
You've made quite a reputation for yourself.
过来 给玛德琳阿姨一个拥抱
Come here. Give Auntie Madeleine a hug.
为什么现在回来?
Why come back now?
我需要干净的枪...
I needed clean guns...
我猜我需要一个理由
and I guess I needed an excuse.
收藏不错
Nice collection.
你要好好照顾它们
And you take good care of them.
让我猜猜 你是多愁善感型
Let me guess. You're the sentimental type.
浪漫
Ro-man-tique.
多愁善感的人做这个不会长久
Sentimental types don't last long doing this.
所以 我不认为我是多愁善感型
So, no. I don't think I'm the sentimental type.
汤米战斧
Tommy Tomahawk.
我到处找它
I looked everywhere for him.
对 很抱歉
Yeah, sorry about that.
那么...
So...
你是个理想主义者
you're an idealist.
不 也许我没有类型
Nope. Maybe I don't have a type.
每个人都有自己的类型
Everybody has a type.
- 每个人  - 嗯
- Everybody.  - Mm-hmm.
也许我是专业型?
Maybe I'm the professional type?
啊 守旧派
Ah. Old school.
“没有女人 就没有孩子”类型
"No women, no children" type.
女人是公平的游戏
Women are fair game.
性别平等
Gender equality.
非常进步
Very progressive.
她是个女权主义者
She's a feminist.
很好
Fine.
你要把握生活
You get to live.
我们会让这些消失
We'll make these disappear
然后给你一些新的 干净的书
and get you into some new, clean books.
你需要一本简·奥斯汀的书
You'll need a Jane Austen.
夏洛蒂·勃朗特的
A Charlotte Brontë.
还有弗吉尼亚·伍尔夫的
And a Virginia Woolf.
噢 还有阿加莎·克里斯蒂的
Oh, and an Agatha Christie.
为阅读
For reading.
求你
Please.
我需要解释这事
I need to answer this.
你得去感谢上帝我没心情杀人
You need to walk away and thank God I'm not in a killing mood.
我别无选择
I got no choice.
- 不  - 够了
- No!  - Enough!
想玩昂贵的游戏吗?
Playing hard to get?
那并不明智 白痴
Not very smart, moron.
除非你想让我把你的小公主撕碎送回来
Not unless you want me to send your little princess back in pieces.
你正好有60分钟
You have exactly 60 minutes
把钱带到保龄球馆
to bring the money to the Gutterball bowling alley.
晚一分钟
A minute late,
她就会和虫子一起庆祝她的九岁生日了
and she'll be celebrating her ninth birthday with the worms.
60分钟
60 minutes.
求你了
Please.
那是我女儿
It's my daughter.
♪ 昨日 ♪
♪ Yesterday ♪
♪ 你得过且过 ♪
♪ Any way you made it was just fine ♪
糟了
Fuck me.
♪ 去追忆 ♪
♪ Try to remember ♪
♪ 那时的九月 ♪
♪ The kind of September ♪
我去叫医生
I'll get the doctor.
把枪放在饼干罐子里
Guns go in the cookie jar.
- 嘿 好久没见到你了  - 嗯
- Hey. Haven't seen you in a while.  - Hmm.
你带来了一个新朋友
And you brought a new friend.
- 怎么回事?  - 我做的
- What the hell happened?  - I happened.
治疗他
Just fix him.
我要他在十分钟内站起来
I need him on his feet in ten minutes.
噢
Ooh.
他哪儿也去不了
He's not going anywhere.
十分钟肯定不行
Not in ten minutes.
也许永远都不行
Maybe not ever.
- 那我们该怎么做?  - “我们”?
- So what can we do?  - "We"?
好吧 你可以从不射人做起
Well, you can start by not shooting people.
拜托 我的艾米丽
Please. My Emily.
- 没时间了  - 嘘
- There's no time.  - Shh.
放松点 深吸一口气
Just relax. Take it in deep.
那是笑气吗?
Is that laughing gas?
当然
Well, duh.
让他能站起来就行
Just patch him up.
我很快就回来
I'll be back soon.
他最好能走
He'd better be functional.
她很烦人 不是吗?
She's quite annoying, isn't she?
我在跟谁说话?
Who am I talking to?
肚子被她射一枪的那个人吗?
The guy that she shot in the stomach?
- 完成了吗?  - 计划有变
- Is it done?  - There's a change of plan.
你在说什么? 什么意思?
What are you talking about? What does that mean?
他们绑架了他的小女儿 那就是他偷钱的原因
They kidnapped his little girl. That's why he stole the money.
如果我15分钟内不到保龄球馆 他们会杀了她
If I'm not at the Gutterball in 15 minutes, they'll kill her.
山姆 没你想的那么简单 快把钱拿回来
Sam, you're not thinking straight. Just bring the money back, now!
我只需要半小时 等我放了她就把钱带回来
I just need half an hour. I'll release her and bring the money.
好吧 听我说 山姆
Okay. Listen to me, Sam.
如果你搞砸了 他们会下格杀令的
If you screw this one up, they will give the kill order.
我无法阻止他们
And I won't be able to stop them.
她只是个小女孩
She's just a little girl.
我不能看着她死
I can't leave her to die.
- 很抱歉  - 你不准挂电话
- I'm sorry.  - Don't you dare hang up on me.
- 很抱歉  - 你不...
- I'm sorry.  - Don't you...
妈的
Fuck.
去保龄馆 跟她讲明道理
Go to the Gutterball. Try to reason with her.
把钱拿回来
Bring back the money.
等等
Wait.
我刚才说“跟她讲明道理”
Now, when I say "reason with her,"
意思是不动枪 不动刀
I mean no guns, no knives.
她要活着回来
She comes back alive.
- 明白了吗?  - 明白
- Understood?  - Yeah.
还有 等等...
And for God's sake...
小心点
be careful.
记住你们是去和谁打交道
Remember who you're dealing with.
还在等什么? 快去
What are you waiting for? Go.
山姆杀的一个人是吉姆·麦克莱斯特的儿子
One of the men Sam killed was Jim McAlester's son.
你确定是麦克莱斯特的儿子吗?
Are you sure it was McAlester's kid?
确定
Yes.
董事会马上就到
The board is on its way.
该死 山姆
Goddammit, Sam.
你他妈是谁?
Who the fuck are you?
拿到你的钱的人
Just someone who has your money.
我要那个女孩
I want the girl.
她爸爸呢?
Where's Daddy?
他...
He...
出了点意外
had an accident.
他派我来的
He sent me.
你到底要不要钱?
Do you want your money or not?
那女孩现在好好的
The girl got to this point alive.
但如果没我的允许
But if you as much as sneeze
你轻举妄动的话
without my permission,
那她就不会好了
that could be easily rectified.
- 知道了  - 很好
- Got it.  - Good.
现在 看到你后面的储物柜了吗?
Now, see the locker behind you?
把武器和手机放在柜子里
Weapon and phone go in the locker,
还有你穿的外套
along with the clothes you're wearing.
把门关上 它就会上锁
Slam the door shut, and it'll lock.
去街对面的韦斯特菲尔德购物中心
Go to the Westfield Mall across the street.
带上你 手提箱 新衣服
You, the suitcase, the new clothes
还有小女孩的电话
and the little girl's phone.
认真的吗?
Seriously?
十分钟
Ten minutes.
你好 山姆
Hello, Sam.
笨蛋
Bonehead.
- 嘿 山姆  - 山姆
- Hey, Sam.  - Sam.
白痴们
Boneheads.
- 我真的没时间陪你们玩  - 内森很担心你
- I really don't have time for this.  - Nathan's worried about you.
他不希望你做傻事
Doesn't want you to do anything stupid.
你为什么不把手提箱交出来
So why don't you hand over the suitcase,
那样就没人会受伤了
and nobody gets hurt.
回去告诉内森你们试过了 但我粗暴的对待了你们
Go back to Nathan, tell him you tried, but I roughed you up.
噢
Ooh.
你们可以自己打一架以增加真实感
You can beat each other up for added realism.
那很有趣
That's funny.
怎么? 今天没带枪吗?
What? No guns today?
内森不想你受伤
Nathan doesn't want you hurt.
事情还不算太糟
Not too badly, anyway.
噢 真贴心
Oh, that is so sweet.
我也会尽量不杀你们
I'll try not to kill you, too.
♪ 我们能战斗 ♪
♪ We can fight ♪
♪ 战斗 战斗 ♪
♪ Fight, fight ♪
♪ 战斗 战斗 战斗 ♪
♪ Fight, fight, fight ♪
她究竟是谁?
Who the fuck is she?
♪ 我们能战斗 ♪
♪ We can fight ♪
去一楼 怪兽视频区
Ground floor. Video Beast.
你超时了
Cutting it close.
我遇到些小问题
I had a few hiccups.
我们看到你处理那些小问题了 你是不是警察?
We saw what you did with those hiccups. How do we know you're not a cop?
警察能像我那么干吗?
Can a cop do what I just did?
我只想要那个女孩
I just want the girl.
那我们就相安无事了
Then we'll get along just fine.
你后面有辆购物车
There's a shopping cart behind you.
把手提箱放进去
Put the suitcase inside.
然后推过来
Push the shopping cart towards us,
我们也把女孩推给你
and we'll push the girl cart towards you.
一
One.
二
Two.
三
Three.
没事了 你很安全
It's okay. You're safe.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
我们发财了 你们这些了不起的混蛋
We're all stinking rich, you magnificent bastards.
停下该死的车
Stop the fucking car.
天哪
Holy fuck!
你这贪婪的叛徒
You greedy traitor!
不... 不
No... no!
不 不 不
No, no, no!
妈的
Fuck.
有受伤吗?
Anything broken?
- 有流血吗?  - 没有
- Are you bleeding?  - No.
有内出血吗?
Bleeding on the inside?
你怎么知道?
How can you tell?
在心里
It's inside.
你应该没事 走吧
You're probably fine. Let's go.
快跟上
Try to keep up.
你们这些白痴把我藏起来的东西都找到了
I see you morons have found my stash.
这真是个好东西 医生
This is some good shit, doc.
你该为自己感到骄傲
You should be very proud of yourself.
这不是玩具
This is not a toy.
它只是给药用的
It's for medicinal use only.
那么...
So...
谁把你们搞成这样的?
who fucked you up like this?
一个女孩
A girl.
一个女孩就把你们搞得像《行尸走肉》出来的?
A girl made you look like you're from The Walking Dead?
医生 我以前从没这么痛过
I've never felt pain like this before, doc.
她对我们很好 医生 我...
She got us good, doc. I...
我想我再也走不动了
I don't think I'll ever walk again.
这肯定是传染病
There must be an epidemic,
因为我隔壁有个人也有类似症状
'cause I got a guy in the next room who's got similar symptoms.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
意思是...
I mean...
有个女孩也把他搞成这样了
a girl fucked him up, too.
接着说 医生
Keep talking, doc.
你在流血
You're bleeding.
只是擦伤
It's just a scratch.
会感染的
It can get infected.
虫子会钻进去产卵 医生就得锯掉你的胳膊
Worms will get in there and lay eggs. Then they'll have to cut your arm off.
这就是他们在学校里教的东西?
That's what they teach in school these days?
是探索频道
Discovery Channel.
感谢上帝 我们直接去医院
Thank God we're going straight to the hospital.
我爸爸在那里吗?
Is my daddy there?
在
Yeah.
那就是他没来的原因吗?
Is that why he didn't come?
他病了吗?
Is he sick?
他...
He...
没事
It's okay.
你不用帮他撒谎
You don't have to lie for him.
他答应的事从来不兑现
He never comes when he says he will.
这里 我来帮你
Here, just let me help you.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
Sure.
你确定是她吗?
Are you sure it's her?
确定 她送了个被她射伤的人来
Yeah. She dropped off some guy she shot.
她说过会儿回来接他
Said she's going to come back and pick him up later.
钱呢?
And the money?
之前我们看到在她手上
She had it last time we saw her.
那就拿回来
Then get it back.
她还有贵宾待遇吗?
She's still getting the VIP treatment?
- 不惜一切代价  - 好吧 好吧
- Do whatever it takes.  - Alright, alright, alright.
这就是我所说的工作福利
Now that's what I call a work benefit.
跟在我后面 好吗?
Just, uh, stay behind me, okay?
来吧
Come on.
我去叫医生
I'll get the doctor.
她来了
She's here.
胳膊上有枪伤
Shot in the shoulder.
也许你该下班了
Maybe you should take your break now.
那么 我的报酬呢?
So. My payment?
- 噢  - 嘘
- Oh!  - Shh.
转到你的帐户了
Transferred to your account.
现在...
Now...
你有什么计划 医生?
What's the plan, doc?
噢
Oh.
一旦我给她打了这个 她的手臂就会开始麻木
Once I stick her with this, she'll start losing control of her arms.
大约60秒后...
After 60 seconds or so...
她就只有等死了
she's a sitting duck.
受伤了吗? 我来处理
What's wrong with you? Let me do this right.
只是擦伤
It's just a scratch.
哦 伤口会感染
Well, scratches get infected.
你可能因此失去一只胳膊
That's how you lose an arm.
嗯 对 我听说过
Mm. Yeah, I heard.
他怎么了?
What happened to him?
有人开枪射了他
Someone shot him.
我听说是致命伤
I hear that's pretty lethal.
来处理伤口
Let's fix this.
不用 我很好
Don't. I'm good.
相信我 你需要这个
Trust me, you'll need this.
我说了我很好
I said, I'm good.
抱歉 我不是那意思...
I'm sorry, I didn't mean...
你这混蛋...
You motherfu...
- 啊  - 60秒
- Ah!  - 60 seconds!
60秒
60 seconds!
60 seconds.
噢 拜托 拜托
Oh, come on. Come on!
听着 我需要你的帮助
Listen, I need your help.
有坏人要来伤害我们
Some bad men are coming to hurt us.
是杀了我爸爸的人吗?
Those who killed my dad?
我保证我会解释的 但现在我需要你的帮助 好吗?
I promise I'll explain, but right now I need your help, okay?
- 好的  - 很好
- Okay.  - Good.
去拿最大的刀
Grab the biggest knife.
小心刀尖
Careful of the sharp end.
好的...
Okay...
拿胶带
Now grab the tape.
非常好 把刀绑在我手上
Excellent. Tape it to my hand.
36...
32...
现在把枪绑在我另一只手上
Now tape the gun to my other hand.
小心点 上膛了
Careful. It's loaded.
15... 14...
第二回合 婊子
Round two, bitch.
笨蛋?
Boneheads?
你最好准备好
Better get ready!
噢 感谢上帝 只有你们三个
Oh, thank God it's just you three.
有一瞬间 我还以为来的是狠角色
For a second there, I thought it was someone dangerous.
你还活着的唯一原因就是内森想这样
The only reason you're still alive is 'cause Nathan wanted it that way.
现在 把我的手指放在扳机上
Now, take my finger and put it on the trigger.
好吧 现在该结束了
Well, it's over now.
我要把你撕成碎片
I'm going to tear you into little pieces.
我会享受这个过程的每一秒
And I'm gonna love every second of it.
好极了 就这么想吧
Great. Hold that thought.
我马上就出来
I'll be right out.
你很勇敢 艾米丽
You're being very brave, Emily.
我要你帮我做最后一件事
I need you to do one last thing for me,
然后躲起来 好吗?
and then go and hide, okay?
好
Okay.
嘿 笨蛋
Hey, Bonehead.
艾米莉
Emily.
你过来接电话
I need you to come grab the phone.
没事 捡起来
It's okay. Just pick it up.
你是个该死的摇滚明星
You are a goddamn rock star.
打开扬声器
Put it on speaker.
最好有人开口说话
Someone better start talking.
那是个...
That was a...
愚蠢的举动 派三个走狗跟着我
jerk move, sending the Three Stooges after me.
你让我们别无选择 山姆
You left us no choice, Sam.
一直都有选择
There's always a choice.
噢 好吧 我们仍然可以解决这个问题
Oh, well, then, we can still figure this out.
只要把钱拿回来
Just bring the money back.
钱没了 手提箱被炸成了碎片
It's gone. The suitcase was blown to 1000 pieces.
噢
Oh.
那真是不幸
That's really unfortunate.
现在怎么办?
So now what?
你知道规则 山姆
Oh, you know the drill, Sam.
你不再受我们保护了
You're no longer under our protection.
在今晚早些时候的大屠杀中
In your little massacre earlier tonight,
你杀错人了
you killed the wrong people.
包括吉姆·麦克莱斯特的儿子
Including Jim McAlester's son.
但我是你派去的
But I was sent by you.
该由公司负责
By The Firm.
那不是重点
It doesn't matter.
这是生意 山姆
This is business, Sam.
你的资产负债表出了问题
And you landed on the wrong side of the balance sheet.
所以...
So...
它必须得到纠正
It needs to be rectified.
这个生意怎么样?
How's this for business?
如果我活着出去
If I get out of this alive,
我会来找你
I'm coming for you.
你们所有人
All of you.
我也希望如此
I would expect no less.
再见 山姆
Goodbye, Sam.
- 什么事?  - 麦克莱斯特先生 我是内森
- Yes?  - Mr. McAlester, this is Nathan.
我是公司人力资源部的主管
I'm the head of the HR department here at The Firm.
你想怎么样?
What do you want?
为了避免我们两个优秀组织之间全面开战
To prevent an all-out war between our two fine organizations,
我们愿意为你提供一位对你损失负责的女士
we would like to offer you the woman responsible for your loss.
所以你们和这事没关系?
So you had nothing to do with this?
我向你保证 这不是公司的经营方式 先生
I can assure you, this is not how The Firm conducts its business, sir.
那件事是个很麻烦的人擅自采取的行动
It was an unsolicited action by a very troubled individual.
现在 我把她最后的位置发给你
Now, I'm sending you her last location.
希望您能满意 先生
I hope this is satisfactory, sir.
现在
For now.
带上所有人
Take everybody.
完事前不要回来
Don't come back until it's done.
- 是内森发来的短信  - 说了什么?
- It's a text message from Nathan.  - What's it say?
“抱歉 孩子 我不能再保护你了 ”
"I'm sorry, child. I can no longer protect you."
“我给你留了个包裹 帮你撑过几天 ”
"I left you a package to help you survive the next few days."
“拿上它 躲起来 ”
"Take it, and disappear."
还有一个地址
Then there's an address.
就在附近
That's close by.
如果是陷阱呢?
What if it's a trap?
能按一下按钮吗? 我们到负二楼
Can you press the button? We're parked on minus two.
记住 多亏了一个八岁的女孩
Just remember, you were spared
你才得以幸免
thanks to an eight-year-old girl.
是八岁零九个月
Eight and three quarters.
抱歉
Sorry.
是八岁零九个月
Eight and three quarters.
你是连环杀手吗?
Are you a serial killer?
什么?
What?
不...
No...
你从哪里学来的这词?
Where did you learn that expression?
- 历史频道  - 哦...
- History Channel.  - Well...
我不是连环杀手
I am not a serial killer.
但是... 你杀人了吗?
But... you kill people?
杀了
Yes.
所以那让你成为杀手
So that makes you a killer.
你还杀了不止一个人
And you've killed more than one.
连续杀的
That is serial.
那个...
It's...
情况比那更复杂
It's more complicated than that.
知道吗 连环杀手精神不稳定
Serial killers are, uh, you know, mentally unstable.
他们出于强迫性冲动杀人
They kill people out of a compulsive urge.
那你为什么要杀他们?
So, why do you kill them?
为了钱吗?
For money?
再说一次 呃...
Again, it's, uh...
那很复杂
It's complicated.
听着 我还需要你的帮助
Look, I'm going to need your help for a little longer.
因为你的手臂还不能动吗?
Because your arms are still paralyzed?
对 之后 我带你去见你妈妈
Yes. After that, I'll get you to your mother.
她很久以前就走了
She left a long time ago.
- 那去找你祖父母  - 他们死了
- To your grandparents, then.  - They're dead.
叔叔呢? 还有其他亲人吗?
Uncles? Anything?
我们会有办法的 好吗?
We'll figure it out, okay?
好的
Okay.
那么 问个无关的问题
So, here's an unrelated question.
你会开车吗?
Do you know how to drive?
我们再试一遍 往左
Let's go over it one more time. Left.
往右
Right.
是的 我已经学会了
Yes, I've got it already.
“D”是行驶“R”是倒车
"D" is for drive. "R" is for reverse.
你只需要踩油门和刹车就行了
And you get to do the easy part, stepping on the gas and breaks.
别自作聪明 启动
Don't be a smart-ass. Turn the key.
挂档
Put it in drive.
走
Let's go.
就这样 坐直身子
That's it. Straighten up.
我会开车了
I'm driving.
对 你会了
Yes, you are.
别担心子弹
Don't worry about the bullets.
马上倒车
Reverse. Now.
往左猛打
Hard left!
- 挂档  - 好
- Put it in drive.  - Yeah.
就这样
That's it.
往左猛打
Hard left.
冲 冲 冲
Go, go, go.
该死的
Damn it!
准备好 往左猛打
Get ready. Hard left.
再往左猛打
And another hard left.
嘘
Shh.
好 倒车
Okay. Put it in reverse.
往右猛打
Hard right!
挂档
Put it in drive.
往左猛打
Hard left.
倒车
Put it in reverse.
好 关掉灯
Okay, kill the lights!
好了 安静 蹲下
Okay, be quiet. Duck down.
就这样 趴下
That's it. Get down.
好 挂档...
Okay. Put it in drive...
闭上眼睛
and close your eyes.
一直往前开
Keep her straight.
一直开
Keep it straight.
你还闭着眼睛吗?
Are your eyes still closed?
- 是的  - 好姑娘
- Yes.  - Good girl.
倒车
Put it in reverse.
我可以听收音机吗?
Can I turn on the radio?
去疯吧
Go nuts.
♪ 虽然这个世界 ♪
♪ Though this world's essentially ♪
♪ 是个荒诞的地方 ♪
♪ An absurd place to be living in ♪
♪ 它不需要气泡消退 ♪
♪ It doesn't call for bubble withdrawal ♪
♪ 我被告知这是生活中的事实 ♪
♪ I've been told it's a fact of life ♪
♪ 虽然这个世界 ♪
♪ Though this world's essentially ♪
♪ 是个荒诞的地方 ♪
♪ An absurd place to be living in ♪
♪ 它不需要气泡消退 ♪
♪ It doesn't call for bubble withdrawal ♪
埃米莉 按门铃
Emily, doorbell.
我不是教过你要随时注意保护自己吗?
Didn't I teach you to always guard your back?
嗨 妈妈
Hi, Mom.
嗨
Hi.
这是 呃...
Is this, um...
我当外婆了吗?
Am I a grandmother?
天哪 不是
God, no.
嗨 我叫艾米丽
Hi. I'm Emily.
- 我是她的徒弟  - 什么?
- I'm her apprentice.  - What?
艾米莉
Emily.
进来
Come.
...需要照顾她一岁大
...the additional burden of needing to care
女儿的额外负担
for her twelve-month-old daughter.
至少一年时间...
It will be at least a year...
那是个可怕的故事
That is a hell of a story.
嗯 一个地狱般的夜晚
Mm. Hell of a night.
嗯... 试着摆动手指
Um... Try wiggling your fingers.
- 感觉很快就能恢复  - 是啊 已经可以动了
- Feeling should come back in no time.  - Yeah, it's already working.
太好了
Excellent.
你看起来真不错 你吃得好吗?
You look really good. Are you eating well?
别说废话了 妈
Cut the crap, Ma.
过去15年你都去哪儿了?
Where have you been for the last 15 years?
你的周围
Around.
在看着你
Watching you.
确保你的安全
Making sure you're safe.
伟大的母爱
Great parenting.
很高兴看到你对我的职业感兴趣
Glad to see you taking an interest in my career.
- 我并不想你过这种生活  - 那你想什么样的生活?
- I never wanted this life for you.  - How's that working out for you?
我想和你还有你的阿姨们在一起 但我不能
I wanted to stay with you and your aunts, but I couldn't.
为什么不能?
Why not?
因为我搞砸了
Because I fucked up.
我搞砸了
I fucked up.
我怀你的时候还很年轻
I was young when I had you.
我们离开伦敦 跟着你父亲来到这里 他死的时候...
We left London, followed your father here. When he died...
他被谋杀的时候
When he was murdered.
他被谋杀时 你还是个婴儿 我一无所有
When he was murdered, you were a baby. I had nothing.
没钱 无处可去
No money, nowhere to go.
我在你爸爸的工作中认识了安娜·梅
I knew Anna May from your dad's work.
她和其他阿姨收留了我们
She and the other aunts took us in.
那我一生中最美好的时光
The best years of my life.
也是我的
Me too.
12年后 我知道了是谁杀了你爸爸
Fast-forward twelve years, and I find out who shot your dad.
俄国人吗?
The Russians?
餐厅里的俄国人?
The Russians from the diner?
一旦我知道了他对我们做了什么 我就不可能
Once I knew, I couldn't let him walk around enjoying life...
再让他优哉游哉的享受生活
knowing what he did to us.
但他和公司有关系 杀他要付出代价
But he was in bed with The Firm, so there was a price to pay.
一旦我杀了他 我就会被打上印记
Once I killed him, there was a mark on my back.
我不能带你一起去
I couldn't take you with me.
我不能拿你的生命冒险
I couldn't risk your life.
所以我让内森保证会保护你的安全
So I made Nathan promise to keep you safe.
我想那已经结束了
I guess that's over.
此后的每一天 我都在后悔扣动扳机
There isn't a day that goes by I don't regret pulling that trigger.
但那时 我无法控制自己
But back then, I couldn't help myself.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
那孩子知道你和她爸爸的事吗?
Does the kid know about you and her dad?
不
No.
但她很聪明
But she's smart.
迟早会知道的
She'll figure it out.
当她知道的时候会发生什么?
What happens when she does?
我觉得外面有个坏人
I think there's a bad man outside.
我们必须离开这里
We have to get out of here.
- 计划是什么?  - 你能按一下大厅的按钮吗?
- So, what's the plan?  - Can you press the lobby button?
- 什么计划?  - 拜托 你总是有计划的
- What plan?  - Come on, you always have a plan.
秘密的逃跑路线? 装满枪的仓库?
A secret escape route? A warehouse filled with guns?
我叫了辆优步
I called us an Uber.
- 你在开玩笑吗?  - 没有
- Are you kidding me?  - No.
一辆优步 你到底在说什么?
An Uber. What the hell are you talking about?
我了解你 你制定计划
I know you. You make plans.
然后你制定计划来制定其他计划
And then you make plans to make other plans.
你嘴上起白沫了
You're frothing at the mouth.
那不体面
It's unbecoming.
抓住她们
Get them!
不用难为情
Don't feel bad.
谁都有失手的时候
Could happen to anyone.
我的手还瘫着
My hand is still paralyzed.
是啊 当然是
Yeah, course it is.
- 那就是  - 我知道
- It is.  - I know.
好 女士们 你们先请
Right. After you, ladies.
来 快点
Come on. Hurry up.
- 它通往哪里?  - 该死的纳尼亚王国
- Where does it go?  - Fucking Narnia.
走 进去
Go. In.
- 进去  - 很好
- In!  - Fine.
- 没计划吧?  - 还不是时候
- No plan, huh?  - Now is not the time.
别挡我的路
Out of my way.
- 要帮忙吗 妈妈?  - 不用 谢谢
- Need help, Ma?  - No, thank you.
我有能力...
I'm quite capable...
搞定一个...
of disposing of one...
...愚蠢的炉子
...idiotic grate.
冰箱里乱糟糟的 这完全不能接受
That freezer is a mess. It's completely unacceptable.
- 快  - 你跟我开玩笑吧?
- Come on.  - Are you kidding me?
- 我们得走了  - 去哪儿?
- We have to go.  - Go where?
很显然你的计划是在这里结束
Obviously your plan was to end up here.
- 那是很久以前的事了  - 妈妈...
- That was a long time ago.  - Mom...
- 我不会走进那里  - 妈妈 听着
- I'm not going in there.  - Mom, listen.
我们需要武器和车 需要一间安全的房屋
We need weapons and a car. We need a safe house!
我不确定她们会不会让我进去
I'm not sure they'd let me in!
只有一个办法能找到答案
Only one way to find out.
嘿
Hey.
说真的 我还是觉得这是个烂主意
For the record, I still think this is a shit idea.
玛德琳?
Madeleine?
姑娘们 我觉得我见鬼了
Girls, I think I see a ghost.
- 嗨 玛德琳  - 嗨 斯佳丽
- Hi, Madeleine.  - Hi, Scarlet.
弗洛伦丝
Florence.
- 嗨 安娜·梅  - 不
- Hi, Anna May.  - No.
不 不 你别说话
No, no. You don't get to talk.
因为你是鬼魂 鬼魂是不会说话的
Because you're a ghost, and ghosts can't talk.
你知道我是怎么知道的吗?
You know how I know that?
我们可以稍后再说这个吗?
Can we do this later?
因为如果鬼魂能说话
Because if ghosts could talk,
它们会在消失前说些什么
they would say something before disappearing.
或者至少留个纸条 但它们做不到
Or at least leave a note. But they can't.
所以 事实上 你是个鬼魂
So, ipso facto, you're a ghost.
- 我很抱歉  - 去你的
- I'm sorry.  - Fuck you.
注意言辞 安娜·梅 这里有个孩子
Language, Anna May. There's a child present.
很好
Fine.
- 去你的  - 去你的
- Fudge you.  - Fudge you.
Fudge 是 Fuck 的委婉表述
去你的
Fudge you!
为什么会有个小孩在我们的营业场所?
And why is there a toddler in our place of business?
剪辑版行吗?
The short version?
请说
Please.
她父亲被杀 她无处可去
Her father was killed and she has nowhere else to go.
我被公司裁了
I was downsized by The Firm,
他们把我扔给麦克莱斯特那些没完没了的暴徒
and they fed me to McAlester's endless supply of thugs.
然后你决定来这里?
And you decided to come here?
我们能在更方便的时候回来吗?
Shall we return at a more convenient time?
也许你应该
Maybe you should.
好像每次你来这里
It seems like whenever you come here,
都会带来一场战争
you bring a war with you.
带上你的问题...
Bring your problems...
我们需要进行表决
We need to table this.
附议
Seconded.
我们下去吧
Let's go down.
带艾米丽走
Go and take Emily.
我来争取点时间
I'll buy us some time.
我想我该留下
I think I should stay.
不
No.
是我搞砸的
I screwed this up.
我会处理我自己惹的麻烦
I'll clean up my own mess.
等我解决了他们 在餐厅见
We'll meet at the diner once I've finished them off.
走
Go.
拜托
Please.
来吧
Come.
你确定吗? 我可以练练打靶
Are you sure? I could use the target practice.
嗯
Mm-mm.
安娜·梅是对的
Anna May was right.
我不该把你们牵扯进来
I shouldn't have dragged you into this.
我要和你在一起
I'm staying with you.
不 不 你不能
No. No, you're not.
你去地下室 那里很安全
You're going to the basement, where it's safe.
但你需要我 我是你的徒弟
But you need me. I'm your apprentice.
好吧 听着 艾米莉
Okay, listen, Emily.
坏人来了 我真的需要你和我妈妈一起走
The bad men are coming. I really need you to go with my mom.
不 我想和你在一起
No! I want to stay with you.
- 你不能  - 但为什么?
- You can't.  - But why?
因为...
Because...
因为我杀了你父亲
Because I killed your father.
你撒谎 你只是想让我走
You're lying. You just want to get rid of me.
你爸爸他 呃...
Your dad, he, um...
他偷了一些坏人的东西
He stole from some very bad people.
他们雇了我
And they hired me.
我开枪打了他
And I shot him.
来 走吧
Come on. Let's go.
我需要武器
I need weapons.
试试自助部分
Try the self-help section.
- 我必须帮她  - 你用得着我同意吗?
- I have to help her.  - You need my permission?
- 我不能再抛弃她了  - 为什么? 这个你很在行
- I can't bail on her again.  - Why? You're good at it.
很抱歉我当时没和你们一起留下 我无法放弃复仇
I'm sorry I couldn't give it up back then and just stay here with you.
你是人类
You're human.
你搞砸了
You screwed up.
我只能想象丢下她是多么痛苦
I can only imagine how painful it was leaving her behind.
把我们都抛诸身后
Leaving us all behind.
但她长大后会是个好女人
But she grew up to be a fine woman.
我从没想要她过这种生活
I never wanted this life for her.
也许这是命中注定
Maybe it was meant to be.
或者她想和她妈妈一样
Or maybe she wanted to be just like her mother.
我想你了
I missed you.
我们为你留了这些“女士”
We kept these ladies for you.
我们在餐厅见
Just meet us at the diner.
完好无损的回来 好吗?
Come back in one piece, okay?
你们两个
Both of you.
混蛋
Motherfucker!
有受伤吗?
Is anything broken?
- 有流血吗?  - 我很好
- Are you bleeding?  - I'm fine.
有内出血吗?
Bleeding on the inside?
其余的人都来了
The rest of them are coming.
说声谢谢会要你命吗?
Would it kill you to say thank you?
你仍然可以走 妈妈 我掩护你
You can still go, Ma. I'll cover you.
然后就错过所有的乐趣?
And miss all the fun?
与狼共舞的女人
Women Who Run with the Wolves.
- 唤醒内心的巨人  - 弹药呢?
- Awakening the Giant Within.  - Ammo?
如何赢得朋友并影响他人
How to Win Friends and Influence People.
你该远离这种职业的
You should've stayed away from this line of work.
你开玩笑吧 妈?
Are you kidding, Ma?
你离开后
You left.
杀人就是我唯一会做的事
Killing people was the only thing I knew how to do.
好吧 也许这不是养育孩子的最佳环境
Okay, maybe it wasn't the best environment to raise a child in.
你这么想的?
You think?
是环境造就了你
It made you who you are.
至少我们可以同意这一点
At least we can agree on that.
你是一个坚强 聪明 令人印象深刻的年轻女子
And you are a strong, smart, incredibly impressive young woman.
这世上没有一个人能让我和她一起杀人
There's not a single person on earth I'd rather kill people with.
谢谢 妈妈
Thanks, Ma.
你真强壮 你不可能才8岁零9个月
You're so strong! You can't be 8 and three quarters.
我是
I am.
你确定你不是28岁零9个月?
You sure you're not 28 and three quarters?
安娜·梅 玛德琳 过来看看这个
Anna May, Madeleine. Come and see this.
噢
Oh.
我们不走了
We're not leaving.
斯佳丽还是个图书管理员 不管她是不是个混蛋
Scarlet's still a librarian, no matter if she's an asshole.
- 注意言辞  - 好吧
- Language.  - Right.
- 所以这些...  - 蠢蛋
- So these...  - Jerks.
...上面那些蠢蛋
...jerks up there
他们犯了一生中最大的错误
just made the biggest mistake of their lives.
他们闯进我们的图书馆 威胁我们的血肉之躯
They stepped into our library and threatened our own flesh and blood.
他们逼迫不了我们
They're not gonna push us around.
他们吓不跑我们 现在该结束了
They're not gonna scare us off. This ends now.
马德琳 把面包车准备好
Madeleine, finish getting the van ready.
弗洛伦丝 你和我去那里减人
Florence, you and I are going up there to thin the herd.
我们要让毁灭苍穹砸在那些混球头上
We're gonna bring the sky down on their mother-fudging heads.
都赞成吗?
All in favor?
- 赞成  - 赞成
- Aye.  - Aye.
赞成
Aye.
动议通过
Motion carried.
你觉得你有机会吗?
You think you have a chance here?
我有一支军队
I have an army.
噢 是吗? 我有我妈妈
Oh, yeah? Well, I've got my mom.
我希望我们有更多时间 妈妈
I wish we had more time, Ma.
要质量 不要数量
It's quality, not quantity.
振作起来
Chin up.
你为什么不出来 我会一枪爆了你的头
Why don't you come out, and I'll put a bullet through your head?
保证又快又好
Nice and quick.
你为什么不先干一下自己呢?
Why don't you go fudge yourself?
如果你要我那么做 我会朝你肚子开枪
If you make me work for it, I'll shoot you in the stomach.
然后我们会玩得很开心
Then we'll have some real fun together.
嘿 笨蛋
Hey, dum-dums.
嘿 白痴们 接住这些
Hey, idiots. Catch these.
白痴去左边 蠢货去右边
Idiots to the left. Morons to the right.
其他笨蛋呆在这里杀了那两个
The rest of you knuckleheads stay here and kill those two.
嘘
Shh.
把这戴上
Put these on.
我要弄出点声音
I'm gonna make a little noise,
所以开大音量
so play it loud.
你能帮我吗?
Can you do that for me?
♪ 噢 来吧 来吧 ♪
♪ Oh come on, come on ♪
♪ 来吧 来吧 ♪
♪ Come on, come on ♪
♪ 我是否让你感觉 ♪
♪ Didn't I make you feel ♪
♪ 你独一无二 ♪
♪ Like you were the only man ♪
♪ 耶 是否我给了你几乎所有 ♪
♪ Yeah Didn't I give you nearly everything ♪
♪ 超过任何一个女人可以给你的 ♪
♪ That a woman possibly can ♪
♪ 亲爱的 你知道我给了 ♪
♪ Honey, you know I did ♪
♪ 每次我都告诉我自己 ♪
♪ But each time I tell myself that I ♪
♪ 哦 我想我受够了 但我就是想让你知道 宝贝 ♪
♪ Well, I think I've had enough But I'm gonna show you, baby ♪
♪ 女人也可以很坚强 ♪
♪ That a woman can be tough ♪
♪ 我想让你来吧 ♪
♪ I want you to come on ♪
♪ 来吧 来吧 ♪
♪ Come on, come on ♪
♪ 过来拿走它 ♪
♪ Come on and take it ♪
♪ 拿走我最后一块心 就现在 宝贝 ♪
♪ Take another little piece of my heart Now, baby ♪
♪ 粉碎它 ♪
♪ Break it ♪
♪ 粉碎我最后一块心 就现在 亲爱的 ♪
♪ Break another little bit of my heart Now, darling ♪
♪ 哦 来吧 ♪
♪ Oh, have a ♪
♪ 宝贝 再拥有我一块心吧 ♪
♪ Have another little piece of my heart Now, baby ♪
♪ 如果你感觉不错 ♪
♪ You know you've got it ♪
♪ 说明你得逞了 ♪
♪ If it makes you feel good ♪
山姆
Sam!
装弹
Reload!
♪ 我需要你来吧 ♪
♪ I need you to come on ♪
♪ 来吧 来吧 来吧 ♪
♪ Come on, come on, come on ♪
♪ 现在拿走它 ♪
♪ Now take it ♪
♪ 拿走我最后一块心 就现在 宝贝 ♪
♪ Take another little piece of my heart Now, baby ♪
♪ 噢 粉碎它 ♪
♪ Oh, break it ♪
♪ 粉碎我最后一块心 就现在 亲爱的 ♪
♪ Break another little bit of my heart Now, darling ♪
♪ 耶 来吧 来个痛快 ♪
♪ Yeah, come on now Oh, have a ♪
♪ 拿走我最后一块心 就现在 宝贝 ♪
♪ Have another little piece of my heart Now, baby ♪
♪ 你知道你得逞了 ♪
♪ You know you've got it ♪
♪ 拿去吧 ♪
♪ Take it ♪
♪ 拿走我最后一块心 就现在 宝贝 ♪
♪ Take another little piece of my heart Now, baby ♪
♪ 噢 拿走 ♪
♪ Oh, take it ♪
♪ 拿走我最后一块心 ♪
♪ Take another little bit of my heart ♪
♪ 再拥有我一块心吧 ♪
♪ Have another little piece of my heart ♪
你头发里有东西
You've got something in your hair.
是一颗牙
It's a tooth.
嘿
Hey.
他...
He...
他抓走了艾米丽
He took Emily.
我没能救下她
I couldn't save her.
没事的
It's okay.
我们会救她回来
We'll get her back.
那太好了...
It was nice...
这下图书馆又有个孩子了
having a kid in the library again.
嗯?
Huh?
“对我来说 生活没有什么乐趣”
"There is little joy in life for me"
“坟墓里也没有什么恐惧”
"And little terror in the grave"
“在我生命最后的时刻”
"I've lived the parting hour to see"
“看到了一个我愿意为拯救她而死的人”
"Of one I would have died to save"
哦 那真让人兴奋 我很久没杀过人了
Well, that was exciting. Been a long time since I killed someone.
让我和艾米丽说话
Let me talk to Emily.
真是悲剧啊
It's a real tragedy
我们这行那些可怜的孤儿怎么办 你知道吗?
what happens to poor orphans in our line of work, you know?
真让人难过
It's really quite sad.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
我叔叔坚持要见你
My uncle insists on meeting you.
他说 只有活剥了你
He says, skinning you alive will let him
才能抚平他的悲伤
work through his, uh, grief.
这要求不过分 是吧?
That's not too much to ask, is it?
如果我去见你
If I come to you,
就放了艾米丽
Emily goes free.
并不再牵涉其他人
And everyone else is off the table.
好吧 我们说定了
Okay, we have a deal.
在餐厅
The diner.
迫不及待了
Can't wait.
我们得走了
We gotta go.
你不能把自己交给那些禽兽
You can't just hand yourself over to those animals.
他们不能带枪进餐厅
They can't bring guns into the diner.
- 这是艾米丽最好的机会  - 这是自杀任务
- It's Emily's best chance.  - It's a suicide mission.
好吧 谁还有计划吗? 嗯?
Well, someone else got a plan? Hmm?
我... 我现在不知道 不
I, uh... I don't right now, no.
但是你 妈妈
But it's you, Mom.
你总是有计划的
You always have a plan.
抱歉
Sorry.
那我想这就是再见了
Then I guess this is goodbye.
他们在等你 亲爱的
They're waiting for you, honey.
谢谢 萝丝
Thanks, Rose.
他们伤害你了吗?
Did they hurt you?
这是漫长的一天
It's been a long day.
很快就会结束了 好吗?
It's gonna be over soon, okay?
好的
Okay.
你是个特别的孩子 艾米丽
You're a special kid, Emily.
我希望我有更多的时间来了解你
I wish I had more time to get to know you.
我叫吉姆
I'm Jim.
萨曼莎
Samantha.
你知道吗 萨曼莎...
You know, Samantha...
我一直认为自己是个女权主义者
I've always considered myself a feminist.
我第一个女儿出生时 我非常高兴
When my first daughter was born, I was over the moon.
把房间刷成粉红色
Painted half the house pink.
墙上都是独角兽和棒棒糖
It was all unicorns and lollipops.
后来我的第二个女儿出生了
And my second daughter was born.
接着是第三个和第四个
And the third and the fourth.
女孩们...
Girls...
总是在餐桌旁低语
always whispering at the dining table.
总是在黑暗的角落里咯咯笑
Always giggling in dark corners.
我爱我的女儿们
I love my girls.
但我不懂她们
But I don't understand them.
然后我儿子出生了
Then my son was born.
这是不同的
It was different.
原因很简单
Simple.
我们彼此了解
We understood each other.
我不再孤单了
And I wasn't alone any more.
我知道...
I know...
那只是你的工作 他...
it was just a job to you, and he was...
在错误的时间出现在错误的地点
in the wrong place at the wrong time.
这些都不重要了
None of that matters,
因为你把他从我身边带走了
because you took him away from me.
我要对你做可怕的事 萨曼莎
I'm going to do terrible things to you, Samantha.
你将承受比你想象的更多的痛苦
You're going to suffer more than you thought even possible.
因为你又让我在自己家里变成了陌生人
Because you have made me a stranger in my own home again.
不管怎样...
For what it's worth...
你儿子的事我很抱歉
I am very sorry about your son.
谢谢你 萨曼莎
Thank you, Samantha.
那就让女孩走吧
Just let the girl go.
还不行
Not yet.
我们说好的
We had a deal.
我是个信守承诺的人
And I'm a man of my word.
我会让那女孩走的 毫发无损
I will set the girl free, unharmed.
但只有在她看了我对你做的事之后
But only after she's watched what I do to you.
拜托
Please.
拜托了 我...
Please, I...
我愿做任何事
I will do anything.
先别乞求
Don't start begging yet.
有足够的时间来做这件事
There's plenty of time for that.
- 还需要点什么吗?  - 不用 我们很好
- Can I get you something?  - No, we're just fine.
再来点咖啡 或者苹果派?
Maybe some more coffee, or apple pie?
如果我不得不再告诉你“不用” 那会有后果的
If I have to tell you no again, there will be consequences.
嗨 甜心
Hi, sweetheart.
嗨 妈妈
Hi, Mom.
我猜毕竟会有个计划
Guess there was a plan, after all.
我想是这样
Guess so.
你为什么不带艾米丽离开这里?
Why don't you take Emily out of here?
这不是孩子待的地方
It's no place for a kid.
别插手 女士们
Stay out of this, ladies.
这不是你们的事
It's not your fight.
再也没有人会置身事外了
There's no more standing on the sidelines.
我们都必须选边站
We all need to pick a side.
准备好 女士们
Right, ladies.
♪ 你现在必须离开 ♪
♪ You must leave now ♪
♪ 带上你所需要的东西 ♪
♪ Take what you need You think will last ♪
♪ 但是你想保存的东西 ♪
♪ But whatever it is you think you need ♪
♪ 你最好抓紧它 ♪
♪ You better grab it fast ♪
♪ 在那边 你的孤儿持枪而立 ♪
♪ Yonder stands your orphan with his gun ♪
♪ 像烈日下的火焰一样哭泣 ♪
♪ Crying like a fire in the sun ♪
♪ 留心 圣徒正在到来 ♪
♪ Look out The saints are coming through ♪
♪ 一切都将结束 忧郁宝贝 ♪
♪ And it's all over now Baby Blue ♪
♪ 高速公路是为赌徒准备的 最好用好你的直觉 ♪
♪ The highway is for gamblers You'd better use your sense ♪
♪ 看好你从偶然中收集到的所得 ♪
♪ Take whatever you've gathered up From coincidence ♪
♪ 你街区中空手的画匠 ♪
♪ The empty-handed painter From your streets ♪
♪ 正在你的单上绘制疯狂的图案 ♪
♪ Is drawing crazy patterns On your sheets ♪
♪ 天空也好似压迫在你的头上 ♪
♪ The sky too now is folding up on you ♪
♪ 一切都结束了 忧郁宝贝 ♪
♪ And it's all over now Baby Blue ♪
♪ 一切都结束了 ♪
♪ It's all over ♪
♪ 忧郁宝贝 ♪
♪ Baby Blue ♪
♪ 一切都结束了 宝贝 ♪
♪ It's all over, baby ♪
♪ 忧郁宝贝 ♪
♪ Baby Blue ♪
艾米莉
Emily.
很抱歉我杀了你父亲 艾米莉
I am so sorry I killed your father, Emily.
如果我能收回...
If I could take it back...
我知道
I know.
但你也想救他
But you tried to save him.
仍然想
Still.
然后你救了我
And you saved me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
另外... 我知道你只是扣动扳机
Besides... I know you just pulled the trigger.
我知道有人让你那么做
I know there was someone else who told you what to do.
是谁派你去找我父亲的?
Who sent you to my father?
有一群人称自己为“公司”
There's a group of men called The Firm.
是... 是个女童子军
It's a... It's a girl scout.
叫她离开
Get rid of her.
不 等等
No, wait.
他们已经运作很久很久了
They've been running things for a long, long time.
他们制定了所有规则...
They make all the rules and...
并根据需要随时改变规则
change them when it fits their needs.
他们认为自己不可触碰
They think they're untouchable.
他们认为他们可以逃避任何惩罚
They think they can get away with anything.
但他们不会 对吧?
But they won't, right?
对
No.
他们不会
They won't.
不再是了
Not any more.
哦 哦 哦 这里有些什么?
Well, well, well. What do we have here?
我在卖饼干
I'm selling cookies.
噢 真的吗? 她们在哪?
Oh, really? Uh, where are they?
你就是我经常听说的那个小女孩 不是吗?
You're the little girl that I've heard so much about, aren't you?
他们这么看不起我 竟然派个孩子来帮她们干脏活?
They think so little of me they sent a child to do their dirty work?
坦率的说 我受辱了
I'm insulted, frankly.
“看看你的心”?
"Look into your heart"?
该死
Fuck me.
你能听见我说话吗?
Can you hear me?
清清楚楚
Loud and clear.
我们都活得好好的
We're both alive and well.
那就到此为止吧
That's the way it's gonna stay.
拜托 山姆 你知道那不取决于我
Come on, Sam. You know that's not up to me.
但你现在有机会结束这一切
You get one chance to end this now.
几年前 我妈妈搞砸了 扣错了扳机
Years ago, my mom screwed up and pulled the wrong trigger.
我没有犯同样的错误
I'm not making the same mistake.
你面前的那个小女孩未来可期
That little girl in front of you will have a future.
去告诉合伙人 我们知道他们在哪里工作
Go back to the partners and tell them we know where they work,
他们住在哪里
where they live.
我们可以杀他们100次而他们却无法知晓我们的到来
We can kill them 100 times over without them ever seeing us coming.
告诉他们 他们只是因为一个
Tell them they were only spared
八岁的女孩而得以幸免
because of an eight-year-old girl.
是八岁零九个月
Eight and three quarters.
抱歉 是八岁零九个月
Sorry. Eight and three quarters.
明白了吗?
Got it?
明白
Got it.
现在 闭上眼睛数到十
Now, close your eyes and count to ten.
数慢点
Slow.
一...
One...
二...
two...
三...
three...
四...
four...
五...
five...
六...
six...
七...
seven...
八...
eight...
九...
nine...
十
ten.
我可以开车吗?
Can I drive?
不行
No.
那我能听收音机吗?
Can I turn on the radio, then?
去疯吧 小姑娘
Go nuts, baby girl.
好了各位 是时候上路了
Right folks, time to hit the road.
保重 那边见
Take care, and see you on the other side.
♪ 我们在高速公路上相遇并在车里同处 ♪
♪ Well I got us on a highway I got us in a car ♪
♪ 我们比以往任何时候都要放纵 ♪
♪ I got us going faster Than we've ever gone before ♪
♪ 我们在高速公路上相遇并在车里缠绵 ♪
♪ I got us on a highway I got us in a car ♪
♪ 我们比以往任何时候都要不羁 ♪
♪ I got us going faster Than we've ever gone before ♪
♪ 然而我知道我们并不会天长地久 ♪
♪ And I know It ain't gonna last ♪
♪ 我也知道我们不会走到旅程终途
♪ And I know It ain't gonna last
♪ 当我看到你的目光降临 ♪
♪ When I see your eyes arrive ♪
♪ 它们像前车窗上的两个虫子一样爆炸 ♪
♪ They explode like two bugs on glass ♪
♪ 在远远的海上 深海之中 ♪
♪ Far above the ocean Deep under the sea ♪
♪ 有一条河流是因你我而干涸 ♪
♪ There's a river running dry 'Cos of you and me ♪
♪ 在远远的海上 深海之中 ♪
♪ Far above the ocean Deep under the sea ♪
♪ 有一条河流是因你我而干涸 ♪
♪ There's a river running dry 'Cos of you and me ♪
♪ 然而我知道我们并不会天长地久 ♪
♪ And I know It ain't gonna last ♪
♪ 我也知道我们不会走到旅程终途 ♪
♪ 然而我知道我们并不会天长地久 ♪
♪ And I know It ain't gonna last ♪
♪ 我也知道我们不会走到旅程终途 ♪
♪ 而且我也知道这段情不会长久... ♪
♪ And I know It ain't gonna last... ♪
♪ 这段情不会长久... ♪
♪ It ain't gonna last... ♪